Tel: +82 (10) 6602 9306 Email: <u>rtkhanas@gmail.com</u>

Address: 2903ho 101dong 221, Seoun-ro, Seocho-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea, 06608

Full stack engineer having experience in front-end, middle-tier and back-end engineering. Most recent work focused on middle-tier JavaScript and front-end JavaScript development. Things that attract me: open-source software, functional programming, developer productivity, algorithms, performance optimization, difficult problems.

## Project experience

## Botish Platform, Samsung Electronics

A service for making chat-bots for multiple platforms easily.

Responsibilities: Design project architecture and set up developer environment. Implement database and REST service for handling requests made by developers and bot users. *Tools and technologies*: Node.js, Docker containers, PostgreSQL, CoffeeScript, React, Babel, Webpack, ESLint, Mocha, CSS.

#### TAU Framework, Samsung Electronics

Web UI Framework for Samsung Tizen devices.

Responsibilities: Make UI components and tools for efficient rendering on low-memory devices.

Achievements: Implemented one of the fastest Virtual-DOM based rendering engines, rendering on different environments such as main thread and web workers.

Tools and technologies: Node.js, Babel, Webpack, ESLint, Mocha, HTML, CSS.

## Recruitment System, InterLogic

An applicant tracking software.

Responsibilities: Apply LinkedIn API for publishing ads; basic optimization of data transitions; implement "statistic" module; support WEB services.

Tools and technologies: APS.NET WebForms, C#, SQL Server, jQuery, etc.

## Form Builder, Perfectial

Control management system for creating web pages.

Responsibilities: Implement dynamic moving, loading, configuring web controls. Tools and technologies: APS.NET WebForms, C#, LINQ, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Windows AZURE, Entity Framework, SQL Server etc.

#### RoboWay, individual project at Lviv Physics and Mathematics Lyceum<sup>1</sup>

A new method for moving a robot from point A to B using genetic algorithms. *Tools and technologies*: Delphi.

## Job experience

- Assistant Engineer, Samsung Electronics, South Korea October 2014—Present
- Software Engineer, InterLogic<sup>2</sup>, Ukraine September 2013 September 2014

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>1</sup> The best high school in Ukraine, acc. to Focus magazine 2015 rankings (2012, 2015). http://focus.ua/

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>2</sup> InterLogic company info: http://interlogic.com.ua/

• Software Engineer, Perfectial<sup>3</sup>, Ukraine — August 2012 – April 2013

## Education

- National University of Ivan Franko<sup>4</sup>, Lviv, Ukraine Bachelor of Informatics & Applied Mathematics, September 2010 – July 2014
- Minor Academy of Sciences of Ukraine, Lviv, Ukraine Member, September 2011 August 2012
- Interlogic, Lviv, Ukraine Intership, September 2009 June 2010

## Skills

## Samsung SW Certificate

Professional Level (3rd out of 4)

# Awards and scholarships

- "The most original idea award" at the national stage of International Competition Intel ISEF 2010
- II place at the National Contest of Research Works in Computer Science by the Academy of Sciences of Ukraine (I place at the Regional Contest) – 2010
- I & II place at the Regional Olympiad in Informatics 2009, 2008 respectively
- InterLogic Scholarship for academic achievements, participation in programming competitions etc. — September 2011 – August 2012

# Languages

Ukrainian (native)

English (fluent)

Russian (fluent)

Polish (intermediate)

# Multicultural experience

Zipline attendant, WonderWorks Attraction<sup>5</sup>, USA — May 2013 – August 2013 *Description*: Work and Travel USA, a program of international cultural exchange.

## Activities and interests

SaaS startups, new technologies, development tools/efficiency, design/architectural patterns, football, traveling.

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>3</sup> Perfectial company info: website <a href="http://perfectial.com/">http://perfectial.com/</a>

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>4</sup> Founded in 1661, top 5 universities in Ukraine, acc. to Scopus: http://studyukraineuniversities.com/scopus-university-ranking-2014/

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>5</sup> WonderWorks company info: http://www.wonderworksonline.com/myrtle-beach/